2023-09-04 04:13:58 INFO - Scenario 'Font settings: Check of increasing and reducing the text size' start 2023-09-04 04:13:58 INFO - Setting application driver using the server on 'https://hub-cloud.browserstack.com/wd/hub' 2023-09-04 04:14:24 INFO - Application on platform 'ANDROID' is ready... 2023-09-04 04:14:24 INFO - Session id - c303bd8b2d8671c8a269868bb6a57e9af53b66b9 2023-09-04 04:14:24 INFO - Step 0 - Close tutorial screen 2023-09-04 04:14:24 INFO - Button 'btnCloseTutorial' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:14:26 INFO - Step 1 - Welcome screen is opened 2023-09-04 04:14:27 INFO - Step 2 - Close welcome screen 2023-09-04 04:14:27 INFO - Button 'btnFindLibrary' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:14:27 INFO - Step 3 - Add library screen is opened 2023-09-04 04:14:28 INFO - Step 4 - Add library "LYRASIS Reads" on Add library screen 2023-09-04 04:14:28 INFO - Button 'Search' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:14:31 INFO - Text Field 'Search' :: Clearing 2023-09-04 04:14:31 INFO - Text Field 'Search' :: Typing 'LYRASIS Reads' 2023-09-04 04:14:33 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:14:34 INFO - Step 5 - Account "LYRASIS Reads" is present on Accounts screen 2023-09-04 04:14:34 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:14:35 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:14:36 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:14:37 INFO - Step 6 - Enter credentials for 'LYRASIS Reads' account 2023-09-04 04:14:38 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:14:38 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:14:39 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:14:40 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:14:41 INFO - Locking credential with barcode 01230000000004 2023-09-04 04:14:41 INFO - There are books on the account: 2023-09-04 04:14:42 INFO - bookName: Adventures of Huckleberry Finn: A Signature Performance by Elijah Wood Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 04:14:42 INFO - bookName: The House in the Cerulean Sea Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 04:14:42 INFO - bookName: The Critique of Practical Reason Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 04:14:42 INFO - bookName: Cryptonomicon Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 04:14:42 INFO - Count of books on the account after opening account: 4 2023-09-04 04:14:42 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Clearing 2023-09-04 04:14:42 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Typing '01230000000004' 2023-09-04 04:14:44 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Clearing 2023-09-04 04:14:44 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Typing '********' 2023-09-04 04:14:46 INFO - Button 'Log in' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:14:51 INFO - Button 'Log ... action' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 04:14:52 INFO - Step 7 - Login is performed successfully 2023-09-04 04:15:12 INFO - Button 'Log ... action' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 04:15:13 INFO - Step 8 - Open Catalog 2023-09-04 04:15:13 INFO - Button 'tabCatalog' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:15:34 INFO - Step 9 - Open search modal 2023-09-04 04:15:54 INFO - Button 'Search' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:15:56 INFO - Step 10 - Search 'available' book of distributor 'Palace Marketplace' and bookType 'EBOOK' from "LYRASIS Reads" and save as 'bookNameInfo' 2023-09-04 04:15:56 INFO - Count of attempts to get random book name without bad symbols-1 2023-09-04 04:15:56 INFO - randomBookName: The Accidental Familiar 2023-09-04 04:15:56 INFO - Error details button is not present 2023-09-04 04:15:56 INFO - Text Field 'Search value input' :: Sending keys 'The Accidental Familiar' 2023-09-04 04:15:58 INFO - Error details button is not present 2023-09-04 04:16:00 INFO - Step 11 - Click GET action button on EBOOK book with 'bookNameInfo' bookName on catalog books screen and save book as 'bookInfo' 2023-09-04 04:16:02 INFO - Label 'lblAuthor' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 04:16:02 INFO - Button 'actionButton' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:16:09 INFO - Step 12 - Open EBOOK book with READ action button and 'bookNameInfo' bookName on catalog books screen and save book as 'bookInfo' 2023-09-04 04:16:09 INFO - Label 'lblAuthor' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 04:16:10 INFO - Label 'lblBookName' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:16:10 INFO - Step 13 - Click READ action button on book details screen 2023-09-04 04:16:11 INFO - Button 'Read' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:16:12 INFO - Step 14 - Scroll page forward from 7 to 9 times 2023-09-04 04:16:12 INFO - Scrolling 8 times on reader epub screen 2023-09-04 04:16:27 INFO - Step 15 - Save font size as 'fontSize' 2023-09-04 04:16:28 INFO - context - NATIVE_APP 2023-09-04 04:16:28 INFO - context - WEBVIEW_org.thepalaceproject.palace 2023-09-04 04:16:29 INFO - pageSourceWithSettingsStart+++++++++++++++++++++++++ 2023-09-04 04:16:29 INFO -

Chapter 1

“You’re talking. Like talking-talking, as in your mouth is moving and words are coming out. Words, I might add, that make total sense.”

“Totally fucked-up, right?”

Poppy McGuillicuddy snorted. So totally. “How is it even possible that you’re talking to me?”

“You have three choices.”

She gulped in the chilled autumn air, inhaling the scent of damp fur and the lingering stench of cheap booze before she sat up straighter and looked the talking cat in the eye (the talking cat).

“Okay, give me my choices. I’m listening.”

The tiny, round black cat began to pace the length of the brick garden wall they’d sat upon when Poppy had demanded she needed air after their “accident”.

The cat stretched, arching its rippling spine, the blue-black of its fur shimmering under the street lamp at the end of the driveway. “First, I just have to make mention. Cooler than coolio costume. Big KISS fan here.”

Poppy preened, fluffing her Afro wig and puffing out her chest to accent the shirt she wore, nude in color with glued-on patches of cotton balls she’d dyed black to mimic copious amounts of chest hair.

“Thanks. I worked extra hard on the star over my eye. Rock and roll hootchie-koo.”

“It totally shows. I’d know you were Paul Stanley if I was blind. Kudos for not going with the obvious choice, too.”

She flapped a hand at the cat and smiled at how clever she’d felt when she’d put this crazy costume together. “Gene’s so overdone. Plus, there’s the tongue thing, you know? I’m just not qualified. Anyway, where were we?”

“Choices,” the cat repeated.

“Right.”

“So let me lay this out for you in list form. You sure you’re ready?”

“Probably not, but I feel like choices are probably moot.”

The feline dipped its shiny, dark head. “No truer words. So here it is in a nutshell. Option one: you can hear me talking to you because you’re fuckin’ nuts. Two: you’re on drugs or have been drugged, which wouldn’t surprise me with that crowd of bananapants stoners in there at that lame excuse for a Halloween party. Three: I’m really talking to you.”

Poppy looked off toward her best friend’s house, sitting just behind the garden wall, and shivered. “I don’t like any of those categories, Alex. Can I have another?”

“Jeopardy doesn’t work that way, Poppy, and you know it,” the cat scolded. “Alex Trebek would be so insulted.”

She gaped at the cat. “How do you know my name?”

The cat scoffed, sitting up straight and affecting a jaunty pose. “Well, it went something like this: ‘Yo, yo, yo, girlz and booooyz! This is Poppy M to the C to the Guill-i-cudd-E in da house, spinnin’ you some oldies but goodies tonight! Who all remembers this mad-ass hit by the Spin Doooctooooors?’ So see? It wasn’t like you kept your name some big secret.”

Right. Her Run DMC impression. She’d been DJ-ing at her old friend Mel’s party before all this had gone down. And what had gone down during that party was nutters. Everything was nutters.

So she said as much to the cat as she rubbed her hands together to keep them warm. “This is insane.”

“Or maybe you are,” the feline offered, dry with sarcasm, sitting back on its haunches and eyeballing her with those wide green orbs.

Poppy cocked her head, remembering the cat’s words. “Insanity… That was one of the choices you laid out, right?”

“Yep. Because sometimes if you’re crazy, it goes hand and hand with delusions. Maybe I’m just a delusion you’ve cooked up in your nutbag head.”

Right. Maybe this was all a delusion. She wasn’t prone to them that she knew of, but how would you know you were having delusions if you were delusional?

She looked down at her phone and the number the cat had told her to call when it realized something was terribly out of whack and talked her into coming outside to handle their little indiscretion with less Blink-182 and Rick James blaring in their ears.

Poppy picked up her phone, letting her feline companion hear the endless drone of ringing on the other end. “I don’t think anyone’s going to pick up. Maybe I dialed the wrong—”

“This is Nina Blackman-Statleon of OOPS, for all your dramatic, life-altering emergency paranormal needs. Recently PA-and ratchety-ass, bag-o’-old-crusty-Paranormal-Council-bones approved as a legitimate source for the stickier paranormal events in your life. So, do tell. How can I help your pathetic, whiny soul today?”

Before Poppy was able to ask what all this talk about crisis and crusty-bones approved business was about, someone cut off the woman on the other end of the line.

“Nina!” a woman with a melodic voice chastised in the background. “Stop that! That could be a real client on the other end in dire need!”

“What, Fakey-Locks? Like they’re not pathetic when they’re all needy and clingy? Please. You asked me to answer the phones tonight, and that’s what I’m doin’. Just shut your over-glossed lips and let me handle this.”

Poppy waivered, rethinking the cat’s nutball suggestion to ring up this hotline called OOPS, one alleging it offered help when you were in paranormal crisis.

But the cat had told her to call this number as if the number itself were a lifeline to God. The talking cat said this was who to call—nay, it had insisted these were the people to bring into this so-called mess.

“Well speak, for catnip’s sake!” the persistent feline urged, nudging her elbow with its peculiarly round head. “We don’t have all stinkin’ night. We need to get this shit straightened out before Familiar Central sends someone in. It won’t look good if we dawdle. You don’t want to look bad in front of your new superiors, do you, Spin Doctor?”

“Poppy!” she blurted out her name, because for some reason it seemed important she be known as something more than the DJ. “My name is Poppy. DJ-ing is just something I do on the side for a little extra cash,” she stated with as much clarity as one could muster when having a conversation with a house pet.

“It’ll be Shit On A Stick if you don’t get crackin’.” The cat’s tail swished in an agitated semi-circle over the surface of the bricks again. “Now talk!” it hissed.

“Hellooo? You’ve got twenty GD seconds before I use my internal GPS and hunt your ass down for crank calling me,” the woman named Nina groused. “I’m gonna start counting now. One…”

Poppy closed her eyes and took a shaky, deep breath of the cold night air, trying to sort through the bits and pieces about familiars and superiors and focus on the fact that this person on the other end of the line was supposed to help her.

With a trembling hand, Poppy finally held the phone up to her ear. “Um, hello?” she whispered into the phone, attempting a calm tone.

No one was going to retell this horror story someday and call Poppy McGuillicuddy a chicken-shit. Not on your life. When witnesses retold this harrowing tale, it would always be prefaced by how brave she’d been.

“I said, how the eff can I help you?” the voice belonging to Nina, the OOPS operator, growled.

Okay, so forget valor. Shit, shit, shit. This was a mistake. A big mistake.

But the cat, the damn talking cat, nudged Poppy again and shouted over the screech of Run DMC still blaring from inside her best friend’s house, “Tell that crabby-AF, pale-faced beast of the female persuasion it’s her friggin’ reluctant-as-hell familiar calling!”

She looked down at the tiny cat with the round head and eyes the color and shape of green marbles and bit the inside of her cheek to keep from screaming.

In and out, Poppy. Breathe in and out. Don’t panic.

“Yo?” Nina prodded, still growling and quite clearly annoyed.

Finally composed, she waded into the conversation pool carefully, because the person on the other end of the phone sounded like everything would be much less explosive if you spoke delicately.

“Your talking cat said I should call you at this number. Did I mention your cat talks? Like, it actually talks. Can I ask you something before we shift into high gear and get to the root of my phone call to you?”

There was a long sigh and then the cantankerous woman said, “You get one question. After that, I get annoyed as all hell, and if you don’t like me now—which, based on my past history with first impressions, I’m guessin’ you’re not a fucking fan yet—then you sure as shit won’t like me when I’m aggravated.”

Poppy swallowed, smoothing the leggings she wore as part of her Paul Stanley costume over her knees. “Just one question? That’s all I get? That seems wholly unfair. This is a crisis hotline, isn’t it?”

“Is that how you want to spend your one question—in negotiations?”

She blinked and came to her senses almost instantly. “No! Sorry. Okay. My one question. Why does your cat talk, lady? Why am I sitting here, outside what was supposed to be a fun, easy DJ-ing gig for some extra vacation money at my best friend’s Halloween Party turned waking nightmare, with a talking cat?”

“Put the GD talking cat on the phone, Cupcake,” Nina’s husky voice demanded.

Poppy paused with a frown and considered how exactly to do that. “Like, hold the phone to its ear? Are you serious?”

“Is the cat talking to you, Princess?” Nina snarled.

Poppy squirmed on the uncomfortable garden wall of bricks she’d perched herself on after this series of unfortunate events had all gone down. “Well, yeah…”

“Then is it a stretch it would talk to me, too, Kumquat? Now put the cat on the GD phone!”

Poppy pulled her cell from her ear and held it up to the cat, putting the phone on speaker. “She wants to talk to you. As in you, the cat. The talking cat.”

There was just no way around this. This was really happening. Or it felt like it was really happening. Maybe someone had dropped acid in her drink? A roofie? No. She’d be passed out if she’d been roofied. Right?

Besides, she was always careful about where she set her water. Even at a party hosted by a friend, she took precautions, because that’s just how Poppy McGuillicuddy rolled. Cautiously.

The cat blinked its overly large, utterly mesmerizing eyes and cocked its head, leaning closer to the phone. “That you, Pale One?”

“That you, Catastrophe?”

“It’s Calamity, you ridiculously, unfairly gorgeous waste of a great ass. We got some shit. Some deep, dark, murky shit going on here.”

“Like?”

Poppy heard the tension in this woman Nina’s voice. She sounded really mad. It almost sounded as if she were the parent and the talking cat was her toddler.

“Calamity? Answer the flippin’ question!” the woman roared in such a forceful way, even the leaves on the trees shook.

The cat, possibly named Calamity—Poppy couldn’t be sure because the woman on the other end of the phone had used two adjectives when addressing said cat—rasped a sigh of full-on exasperation.

“Don’t get your fangs twisted, Blood Lover Lite. Just get here and bring the ditzy blonde with all that lip gloss and hair bleach. Oh, and the nice one who sneaks me the real tuna, not that crap in the can packed in water.”

“Wanda. That’s Wanda, and if she’s sneaking you tuna, I’m going to kick her perfectly mannered ass. What have I told you about tuna, Calamity? What?”

Calamity The Talking Cat lifted her chin. “Oh, blah, blah, blah. Tuna is too rich for my touchy tummy. Blah, blah, blah. Makes me puke all over the carpet in the castle. Blah, blah, blah. You hate cleaning up the chunky effin’ puke. Blah, blah, blah.”

“Exactly. Now, tell me what’s going on, C, or I’m gonna make you wear those stupid sweaters with the glitter on them from the Martha Stewart Collection at PetSmart every day for a GD week.”

Calamity rocked back on her hind paws and gasped in outraged horror. “You wouldn’t! Fuck, those are ugly, you monster.”

“Sooo would,” the husky voice crooned with a tone screaming devilish glee. “I’d damn well grin from ear to ear while I did that shit, too. Now what’s going on? Spit it the fuck out now.”

Calamity rolled to her back, inching along the bricks to scratch her spine, her response rather cavalier, considering the magnitude of the alleged incident. “So there was an accident at a party I’m at, and as a byproduct of this accident, something happened. Not a big deal, really. Nothing I can’t handle.”

“What accident, Calamity? And why the fuck are you crashing parties? What did I tell you about that shit?”

“As I recall,” Calamity drawled. “You said no wedding crashing. There was nothing about party crashing in general.”

“Don’t you mince motherfluffin’ words with me, Calamity! Now knock it the shit off and—”

There was a muffled sound, as though someone was trying to wrestle the phone from Nina, and then a much sweeter, far more affable voice came on the line. “Calamity, honey? It’s Marty. You know the one. The blonde with all the lipstick and hair bleach? Talk to Auntie Marty, Precious, and tell me what happened so we can help. Maybe it’s not such an emergency after all.”

“That’s Marty. Super nice, fashionista, not very brainy. A werewolf, by the way,” Calamity whispered as though no one but Poppy could hear. Clearing her throat, the cat continued. “So here’s the prob in a nutshell. I think. Nothing for certain here, mind you, but I think I turned the party DJ into one of my own.”

“A cat?”

“No, Marty—a familiar. I think I turned the DJ into a familiar.”

“You think?” Auntie Marty repeated, her tone still almost as sweet with only a hint of an angry tremor.

There was more rustling and another muffled, “Give me the damn phone, Ass Sniffer,” before the mean one named Nina was back on the line. “Location!” she bellowed, making Poppy wince. “Now, Calamity!”

As Calamity The Talking Cat rattled off the location, Poppy looked at the inside of her wrist and ran a finger over the raised picture now on her flesh, growing more dazed and confused by the second.

Sure, there was a half-moon tattoo-ish looking thing with a sprinkle of stars across the center of it in a place she had no recollection of ever getting a tattoo. In fact, she didn’t have any tattoos at all. Her mother would kill her if she got a tattoo, but this was what had convinced the cat, er, Calamity, that she was now a familiar.

Whatever one of those was. She vaguely remembered watching Charmed as a teenager and the mention of familiars, but that had been a long time ago, and the definition of one and their place in the witch world were both very vague.

Holding her wrist up, she inspected the mark in question under the light of the streetlamps. Maybe it was one of those temporary tattoos, and this was all a joke? Licking her finger, Poppy scrubbed it over her skin, but the half-moon remained clear as day.

All right. So this wasn’t some kind of joke.

“What in the fresh hell are you doing?” Calamity asked, dancing over the garden wall, swatting at dust particles.

“Trying to figure out if this is all some elaborate prank played on me by my BFF.”

“You mean the skinny one dressed up like Kanye West, guzzling that cheap bottle of Boones Farm like it was her last night on earth while she rocked back and forth pressed up to the guy dressed like Kim Kardashian, who was at least ten years younger than her and stoned half out of his gourd?”

Poppy smiled briefly. Her pal Mel had never graduated college-level drinking. Even at thirty-four, she was still boozing it up like she was twenty. In fact, she was still dating like she was twenty.

She sighed in resignation. “Yeah, that’s her.”

Calamity snorted indignantly, the small puff of air turning to a cloud of condensation. “She couldn’t even make decent appetizers—Triscuits and Vienna sausages in a can do not a party make. Even a heathen troglodyte would turn their nose up at that crap. That in mind, do you really think someone dressed as Kanye West is capable of pulling off some shit like this?”

Poppy put her arm back at her side and looked directly into the cat’s mesmerizing eyes, trying to rationalize—or maybe the better word was minimize—what was currently happening.

“What exactly is this shit? I just have a tattoo I don’t remember getting. So what? Lot’s of people have tattoos they don’t remember getting. In fact, half my night-school college class has tattoos they don’t remember getting. Big deal.”

Calamity cocked her head as though assessing her. “Well, sure. That’s true. You could sweep this shit under the carpet with some implausible, farfetched explanation. But you’re also talking to a cat like Dr. Doolittle’s spirit took possession of your body. So there’s that. What more proof do you need?”

Poppy winced. “Like you said, maybe I’ve been drugged?”

Calamity made a clicking noise in the back of her throat. “You won’t be able to use that excuse when you wake up tomorrow, and you’re in the same boat. Because you’ll still be a familiar, and I’ll still be talking.”

Pulling off the Paul Stanley Afro wig, Poppy ran her hands through her hair and sighed again. “Okay, so if I’m not drugged, and this isn’t some version of Punk’d complete with sound effects and live animation, what is this shit?”

“This shit is bullshit. That’s what this shit is,” a familiar voice from the shadows groused.

As if out of nowhere, three women appeared, their hair billowing about their shoulders in the frigid winds of Staten Island, their strides confident, their eyes focused and glimmering in the night. Like some new millennium Charlie’s Angels, they strode toward her with confidence, all long legs, beautiful clothing, expensive perfume and glittery jewelry.

Well, except for the dark one. She had long legs and the billowy hair for sure, but she wasn’t dressed like she was going to the same party the other two women were. She wore work boots, a thick black hoodie, low-slung black jeans and a big ol’ scowl on her utterly perfect, scarily pale face.

“You Poppy?” she demand-asked, coming to stand in front of her, arms crossed over her hoodie-covered chest.

She gulped, looking up into this woman’s flashing coal-black eyes. “Will a brutal beating follow if I say yes?”

The blonde woman with loads of swirly hair and clacking jewelry nudged the dark-haired woman in the ribs with a frown. “I’m sorry for how abrupt Nina is. You’ll adjust as we move forward. Forget her and focus on me. I’m Marty Flaherty, this ogre is Nina Statleon, and this,” she pointed just over her shoulder to the tall chestnut-haired lady with mahogany highlights, “is Wanda Jefferson. We’re OOPS, and we’re here to help.” Then she smiled, dazzlingly white and perfect.

As though the wind had re-inflated her sails, Poppy jumped up, putting a defensive hand in front of her. “Help with what? This is all crazy. Look, I don’t know what the cat told you or why it even insisted I call you. Forget about the fact that it can speak and has the ability to use a phone. We’ll get to that later. Now, I looked at your website online, and it says you help people in paranormal crisis. I don’t know if that means you host drug interventions for ghosts—do ghosts become addicts or were they addicts before they died and need ongoing afterlife care? For that matter, what does ‘paranormal crisis’ even mean and why am I supposedly having one?”

The woman named Nina reached for Poppy’s wrist so fast, so freakishly fast, Poppy gasped. “I’m gonna ask you to chill the fuck out, okay? Stop gettin’ all jenky with your hands because you don’t want to get defensive with the likes o’ me. Now breathe, Petunia.”

It was almost a relief to have someone give her some direction. Bending at the waist, she let her hands rest on her knees, and her head hang low. “Maybe we should start over and reintroduce ourselves?”

Nina put a hand on the back of her head, keeping her face pointed downward at the driveway. “I said breathe, Rock Star—great costume, by the way. Paul Stanley’s no fucking Barry Manilow, but you killed the makeup. Now, get your shit together. While you do that, I’m gonna kick the living crap out of my damn familiar for ignoring my house rules, and then we’ll make nice, and I’ll explain what we do at OOPS and all that bullshit.”

Poppy blinked as the blood rushed to her head in a swoosh of pounding waves. “The cat’s yours?”

Nina snorted. “It sure as fuck wasn’t my idea, but yeah. She’s mine.”

“It talks.” She realized she kept saying that, but c’mon! Wasn’t anyone else as in awe of that fact?

Nina clucked her tongue in admonishment. “Been down this road, Poppy. You’re getting repetitive. A sure sign you’re playing possum.”

She tried to lift her head, but Nina’s hand was like a vise grip, forcing her to keep her eyes level with her feet. “Possum?”

“Yeah, it’s when everyone says they’re fine while they beat their panic down, bottle it the fuck up or whatever so they can give good face, which always leads to total meltdown. It’s pathetic and ugly, and usually involves tears and loads of the sympathy I’m working really hard to get better at giving because my therapist says I suck ass at it.”

“This is your version of sympathy?”

“This is me working on being sympathetic. Don’t fuck up my flow.”

“So you’ve done this before? This crisis thing?” If that was true, that almost made her feel better. Almost. Though, she still couldn’t quite connect the dots between what had happened back at the house to needing a crisis counselor. Still, she didn’t sense these women were dangerous.

In fact, she was very clear about the notion they weren’t dangerous. Though, why the feeling was so vivid, she couldn’t say. She possessed her own kind of intuition for sure, but it was a very average sort of intuition. This? Well, this sort of intuition was different.

Nina’s patted the back of her head before her cool fingers clasped her neck. “More times than Marty’s got lipsticks. Keep breathing.”

“I’m really dizzy,” Poppy complained, her spine beginning to ache.

“It’s those pants,” Nina commented. “Always wondered how Stanley managed to squeeze into ’em without popping the top of his head off.

A soft hand reached down and grabbed Poppy’s, pulling her up and holding her firm when she stumbled from lack of blood flow. “Let her up, Nina.” The lady named Marty righted Poppy and smiled. “So tell us what happened so we best know how to help you.”

Poppy stared at the woman with eyes of cornflower blue and hair in more shades of blonde than she even knew existed, and thought about her request. She wasn’t quite sure how this had happened…or if anything had really happened at all.

Marty pressed with a warm smile, “Poppy, honey? How did this happen?”

Words escaped her.

But they didn’t escape the cat. It hopped down from the garden wall and wound its long tail around Marty’s legs. “Ask me, Bleached One. I know how it happened.”

The woman named Wanda bent and scooped the cat up, snuggling her close to her porcelain cheek with a smile. “What kind of mischief have you been into now, Miss Calamity?” she asked, her tone oozing indulgence.

Calamity purred in return, curling into Wanda’s arms. “It was an accident, I swear, Wanda.”

Nina tweaked the cat’s ear, her face stern against the backdrop of the dark night. “Quit coddlin’ her like she’s some baby, Wanda. She was out way past curfew, which is bullshit. She damn well knows better. And lay off the tuna when I’m not lookin’. It makes her puke.”

Wanda flapped an irritated hand at Nina before resuming her cuddle with the cat. “Hush. She’s just acting out because you’re so hard on her. Now, tell Auntie Wanda what happened here, Calamity, and I promise there’ll be some warm milk tonight before bed.”

Calamity purred and brushed Wanda’s cheek with her paw. “Okay, it went down like this. M to the C to the Guill-i-cudd-E was spinning records at this lame Halloween party—”

“A party you didn’t ask fucking permission to go to,” Nina growled, her black eyes narrowing as she jammed her hands into her hoodie pockets.

Calamity stopped purring and gave Nina a hard glare. “You don’t ask permission to crash a party, Beastmaster. It’s not a goddamn crash if you ask for entry. Anyway, I was chillin’ to Poppy’s beat and I got a little carried away when I broke out my smooth MC Hammer moves. I tripped on a glass of water, knocked it over on the wiring for the speakers, which I’m pretty sure weren’t up to code, and wham! Almost electrocuted Poppy. So I try to do the right thing by knocking her wee sprite ass out of the way with my magic, but I slipped and fell into her, and then we both fell—”

“Into the puddle of water!” Poppy spat as she retreated from her fog, the entire episode coming together in a clatter of memory. “That’s exactly what happened! When the cat jumped on me, she dug her claws into my shoulder, and I tripped and fell into the water where the speaker wires were. See?” She pulled her pleather jacket with the stars she’d bedazzled on herself away from her shoulder, pointing to the scratch marks to show the women.

Marty winced, leaning in closer to inspect her wounds.

Nina swished a hand at Marty, pointing to her purse. “Dig around in your mom bag there and get this kid some Neosporin, Blondie.”

But Poppy waved a hand in dismissive fashion. “I swear I saw stars and a big flash of light. Then there was this tingle…like a weird shiver that raced all along my limbs, and then the cat was freaking out and yelling at me to come outside and call you before someone, I can’t remember who, came and picked me up—”

“That bitch Cecily from Familiar Central,” Calamity interjected with a scoff. “Swear, she can smell a newb from a realm away. She’s gonna show up here and demand to take DJ Puts The Needle On The Record back to the realm so she can claim her as her own, and I’ll be dipped in cow dung before I’ll let that happen.”

“Claim me?” Poppy squeaked, scanning the dark neighborhood for this woman named Cecily.

Calamity tilted her head so Wanda could scratch her neck. “Yeah. She gets like frequent flier miles for every newb familiar she sucks into her dark void or some shit. If she gets enough miles, she gets to go to some familiar retreat in Baja. Why the fuck should she get all the miles? I did this to ya, I win. That’s how it works with all familiars who are found or made—in your case, accidentally made—rather than born into the realm, by the way. If one of us finds you, it’s our duty to turn you in. Also, if that crazy hag Cecily gets her hands on you, who knows who the hell you’ll end up with. She just doesn’t care the way I do, and because this was my fault, the least I can do is try to make sure you get a good witch.”

A witch? She was getting a witch? What did that mean? Did it mean a job that paid money? Because she could use a job that paid money. God, could she ever.

Nina jammed her hands into her black hoodie pocket. “So let me get this shiz straight. Basically, you zapped a bitch and transferred some of your mojo to her, and that means she’s a familiar now, too? How the hell do you know that for sure?”

Calamity harrumphed at Nina. “All you gotta do is look at her wrist. She does have The Mark, Keeper of My Cage. It’s just like the one on the underside of my paw. We all have ’em.”

Poppy immediately began to back away, but she held up her wrist so they could all see the half-moon shape, which, as was becoming increasingly clear, apparently represented her status as a familiar.

“Hol-ee shitballs,” Nina muttered. “And you’re sure this means she’s like you? I thought familiars were all animals?”

“That’s because you don’t listen when I’m trying to school your sorry ass, Half-Breed!” Calamity exclaimed in a tone screaming exasperation. “Familiars come in all sorts of shapes and sizes these days. Animals are the least likely suspects for prying human eyes, but there are plenty of uprights to be had nowadays. You’d know that if you’d just become a little more involved in the community, you dolt!”

Nina snarled, reaching for Calamity, but Wanda took a step back to avoid her.

Suddenly, Poppy couldn’t take it anymore. Scooping up her Paul Stanley wig from the brick wall, she shook it at the group as though it would ward off impending danger.

“What does like her mean?” she shouted. Everything was moving at the speed of light while she was still stuck on the fact that a cat could talk.

Calamity sighed in what sounded like resignation, as though Poppy should know exactly what she was talking about. “It means we gotta get you to Familiar Central so you can get in the good line to get a nice witch. You do not want to wait for them to assign you somebody or you’ll end up like I did, with a leftover with anger management issues. That’s how I landed this crazy half-breed, scowling-at-everything-that-moves bitch on monster truck wheels.” Calamity lifted her jaw in Nina’s direction.

“A leftover…” Poppy muttered, but that didn’t slow Calamity’s tirade even a little.

“Now, I admit, I was lazy as fuck, and I should’ve gotten my shit together a lot sooner than I did when my old witch died. I lollygagged, hung out, threw back a bunch of brewskies, watched a lot of shitty reality TV and in general took a break from all the hocus-pocus crap. My old witch was a handful. But who knew I’d end up with the bottom of the barrel just because I was on sabbatical? And to add insult to injury, I ended up with an ogre who’s half vampire. Like I know a friggin’ thing about vampires. But there was no talking the head honcho out of this match made in the inner circle of Hell. So here I am—stuck with a psychotic, nay, violent, half-vampire/half-witch. Forever.”

Nina eyeballed Calamity, and to say she wasn’t exactly pleased was likely an understatement. But oddly, her next words were far more levelheaded than Poppy would have expected, even though her fists were tightly clenched at her sides and her teeth could quite possibly crack from the pressure of grinding them.

“We’re working through some shit. Boundaries, rules, crap like that.”

“Yeah,” the cat scoffed, curling into Wanda’s protective hold. “Boundaries and crap. That’s what we’re working through. I hope that helps you sleep at night. Oh, wait. You don’t sleep at night, do you, Blood Sucker?”

Marty grabbed one of Poppy’s hands and held it to her chest, her warm, smooth skin soothing Poppy, lulling her into a sense of security. Probably a false sense of one, but still a comfort. “To say Calamity was a surprise is an understatement. She and Nina are in the adjustment phase of their relationship—still working out the kinks, you know?”

“You mean the phase where she doesn’t fucking do what she’s told?” Nina asked.

Calamity crawled to Wanda’s shoulder and perched herself there. If cats could give dirty looks, she was shooting daggers at Nina. “I’ll say this one more time, Pale Face. I am your guide, your helper, your GD advisor to the magical realm. Not your slave in perpetuity. Got that, you colossal PITA? You can’t tell me what to do. I’m a hundred and fifty years old, not ten!”

Wanda chuckled and scratched Calamity under the chin, burying her face in the cat’s neck. “You tell her, Snookiepuss.”

Nina openly gaped at Wanda, her flawless face a tight mask of anger. “What the fuck is wrong with you, Wanda? Why the hell are you taking her side? Stop gettin’ in the middle of our shit, for Christ’s sake! If she didn’t behave like a motherfluffin’ kid, I wouldn’t treat her like one! I’ve been chasin’ after this toddler on steroids since she got here, putting out fire after fucking fire just as she lights another damn match. Now mind your damn P’s and Q’s!”

Marty popped her glossed lips and clapped her hands, a cheerfully forced smile on her face. “Ladies! Knock it off!” she shouted then squared her shoulders and smoothed her faux fur vest over her waistline. “We have no time to spare while the two of you argue over how Nina parents her unruly familiar. We have a job to do. Let’s do it before this Cecily shows up and steals Calamity’s thunder or Poppy ends up with an ogre like Nina for the rest of her days. Now, what do we do next, Calamity?”

Calamity hopped from Wanda’s shoulder to the ground and stretched. “It’s a doozy of a ride. You sure you’re up for it?”

As Poppy listened to Calamity’s explanation and watched the drama between the women unfold, she remained quiet, dealing with this new feeling she had. This new certainty was maybe a better word.

She knew, without a shadow of a doubt, what these women spoke was the truth. There was no second-guessing, no quibbling. She instinctually knew the cat really could talk. Nina really was half-vampire, half-witch, and Poppy really did have to get to this place called Familiar Central.

She didn’t quite understand this innate sense of the truth; she wasn’t even sure how she was keeping from freaking out about the fact that Nina was a vampire-witch.

Maybe that would come later? For now, she had to take care of this. There was a pressing urgency in her gut that said she needed to trust her instincts.

“Does this familiar thing pay?”

“Like in money?” Calamity asked, cocking her round head.

She needed money. It wasn’t likely Mel was going to pay her now after she’d obliterated her sound system. To make everything worse, she was surely on the verge of being booted from her apartment if she didn’t come up with three months’ rent by next week.

Old Mr. Rush, her landlord, was an understanding guy, a great guy, in fact. But he couldn’t live on nothing any more than she could. And that’s what she’d been paid for spending almost four months on the road in a show that had such low attendance, the audiences were all but taking naps.

Nothing.

That son of a bitch Randall Cranston had run off with what little profit they’d made, leaving her and the rest of the cast high and dry.

She hated leaving her apartment and all the incredible people who’d been her neighbors for almost five years now, but she’d come to the realization her choices were growing slimmer by the day.

She’d even considered going back to her parents in Cincinnati. While she loved them, she didn’t necessarily want to live with them and their paneled walls and meals with a Wheel of Fortune/Jeopardy! double whammy anymore.

So this was a possible answer to all her financial problems.

Besides, she’d done crazier things for cash.

Finally, she said, “Well, yeah, I mean in money. I have to eat.”

“Not in money, no. But it does include room and board. Er, mostly…”

Calamity’s vague answer went by the wayside, almost unheard after the words “room and board.” Looking down at the cat, Poppy nodded with total calm. “I’m ready.”

For the first time since she’d met her, Nina grinned as she scanned Poppy’s face, her glimmering eyes searching. “Holy fuck. You’re serious?”

She was. She didn’t know why she was, but she was. “I am. Let’s go.”

Nina gazed down at Calamity and pointed a long finger at her. “Then let’s get it on before she comes down off her high o’ crazy and changes her mind.”

“Did you bring your wand?” she asked Nina, stretching a paw forward.

Nina made a face, the hard lines of her jaw tightening. “No, I didn’t bring my fucking wand. That shit is like holding a hand grenade. I never know whether I’m going to blow crap up or turn it into a friggin’ animated ice sculpture. I’m not good enough at it yet to carry it around full time. Christ, it was much easier just being a vampire. All I had to do was flash my fangs and shit got done.”

Calamity clucked her tongue. “What have I told you about your wand, you beast? Ya gotta keep it with you at all damn times. It’s like leaving an organ behind.”

“I don’t have any organs.”

“Okay, it’s like leaving your sunscreen behind. Crucially important. I’ve only told you that a bafrillion times, Nina. You do know you just made this shit much harder?”

Poppy blinked. Nina had a wand? “Why does that make shit harder?” she asked.

Calamity snorted. “Hold one minute, and I’ll show you…”

2023-09-04 04:16:29 INFO - pageSourceWithSettingsEnd+++++++++++++++++++++++++ 2023-09-04 04:16:29 INFO - Taking screenshot 2023-09-04 04:16:31 INFO - Test finished - logging out 2023-09-04 04:16:32 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:16:34 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:16:35 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:16:36 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:16:38 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 04:16:39 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 04:16:39 INFO - Button 'Log out' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:16:59 INFO - Button 'Log in' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 04:17:00 INFO - Unlocking credential for current thread 2023-09-04 04:17:00 INFO - isLoggerNullAfterAnnotation-framework.utilities.Logger@1c7e34a7

2023-09-04 04:39:55 INFO - Scenario 'Font settings: Check of font style' start 2023-09-04 04:39:55 INFO - Setting application driver using the server on 'https://hub-cloud.browserstack.com/wd/hub' 2023-09-04 04:40:21 INFO - Application on platform 'ANDROID' is ready... 2023-09-04 04:40:21 INFO - Session id - 390c1dfe5752283b040a106aa96f164180327a65 2023-09-04 04:40:21 INFO - Step 0 - Close tutorial screen 2023-09-04 04:40:22 INFO - Button 'btnCloseTutorial' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:40:23 INFO - Step 1 - Welcome screen is opened 2023-09-04 04:40:24 INFO - Step 2 - Close welcome screen 2023-09-04 04:40:24 INFO - Button 'btnFindLibrary' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:40:24 INFO - Step 3 - Add library screen is opened 2023-09-04 04:40:26 INFO - Step 4 - Add library "LYRASIS Reads" on Add library screen 2023-09-04 04:40:26 INFO - Button 'Search' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:40:27 INFO - Text Field 'Search' :: Clearing 2023-09-04 04:40:27 INFO - Text Field 'Search' :: Typing 'LYRASIS Reads' 2023-09-04 04:40:30 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:40:30 INFO - Step 5 - Account "LYRASIS Reads" is present on Accounts screen 2023-09-04 04:40:30 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:40:31 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:40:32 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:40:34 INFO - Step 6 - Enter credentials for 'LYRASIS Reads' account 2023-09-04 04:40:34 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:40:34 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:40:35 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:40:36 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:40:37 INFO - Locking credential with barcode 01230000000002 2023-09-04 04:40:37 INFO - There are books on the account: 2023-09-04 04:40:38 INFO - bookName: Phantom Lover Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 04:40:38 INFO - bookName: The Black Kids Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 04:40:38 INFO - bookName: The Innovators Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 04:40:38 INFO - bookName: Snow Crash Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 04:40:38 INFO - bookName: The Martian Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 04:40:38 INFO - bookName: Legacy Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 04:40:38 INFO - Books without revoke in link. BookName: Unprotected Distributor: framework.utilities.returningBooksUtil.Distributor@4a13b1d8 2023-09-04 04:40:38 INFO - Books without revoke in link. BookName: Chocolate Cream Pie Murder Distributor: framework.utilities.returningBooksUtil.Distributor@7589cc54 2023-09-04 04:40:38 INFO - bookName: The Ice Queen Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 04:40:38 INFO - Count of books on the account after opening account: 7 2023-09-04 04:40:38 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Clearing 2023-09-04 04:40:38 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Typing '01230000000002' 2023-09-04 04:40:39 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Clearing 2023-09-04 04:40:39 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Typing '********' 2023-09-04 04:40:41 INFO - Button 'Log in' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:40:46 INFO - Button 'Log ... action' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 04:40:46 INFO - Step 7 - Login is performed successfully 2023-09-04 04:41:07 INFO - Button 'Log ... action' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 04:41:07 INFO - Step 8 - Open Catalog 2023-09-04 04:41:07 INFO - Button 'tabCatalog' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:41:31 INFO - Step 9 - Open search modal 2023-09-04 04:41:51 INFO - Button 'Search' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:41:53 INFO - Step 10 - Search 'available' book of distributor 'Palace Marketplace' and bookType 'EBOOK' from "LYRASIS Reads" and save as 'bookNameInfo' 2023-09-04 04:41:53 INFO - Count of attempts to get random book name without bad symbols-1 2023-09-04 04:41:53 INFO - randomBookName: The Dorrance Domain 2023-09-04 04:41:53 INFO - Error details button is not present 2023-09-04 04:41:53 INFO - Text Field 'Search value input' :: Sending keys 'The Dorrance Domain' 2023-09-04 04:41:56 INFO - Error details button is not present 2023-09-04 04:41:58 INFO - Step 11 - Click GET action button on EBOOK book with 'bookNameInfo' bookName on catalog books screen and save book as 'bookInfo' 2023-09-04 04:41:59 INFO - Label 'lblAuthor' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 04:42:00 INFO - Button 'actionButton' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:42:07 INFO - Step 12 - Open EBOOK book with READ action button and 'bookNameInfo' bookName on catalog books screen and save book as 'bookInfo' 2023-09-04 04:42:07 INFO - Label 'lblAuthor' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 04:42:07 INFO - Label 'lblBookName' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:42:08 INFO - Step 13 - Click READ action button on book details screen 2023-09-04 04:42:09 INFO - Button 'Read' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:42:09 INFO - Step 14 - Scroll page forward from 7 to 9 times 2023-09-04 04:42:09 INFO - Scrolling 8 times on reader epub screen 2023-09-04 04:42:26 INFO - Step 15 - Open font settings 2023-09-04 04:42:27 INFO - Button 'btnFontSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:42:27 INFO - Step 16 - Change font style to FONT_SERIF 2023-09-04 04:42:27 INFO - Button 'setFontSerif' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:42:28 INFO - Step 17 - Book text displays in FONT_SERIF font 2023-09-04 04:42:28 INFO - context - NATIVE_APP 2023-09-04 04:42:28 INFO - context - WEBVIEW_org.thepalaceproject.palace 2023-09-04 04:42:29 INFO - pageSourceWithSettingsStart+++++++++++++++++++++++++ 2023-09-04 04:42:30 INFO -

Chapter I

Cooped up

"I wish we didn't have to live in a boarding-house!" said Dorothy Dorrance, flinging herself into an armchair, in her grandmother's room, one May afternoon, about six o'clock.

She made this remark almost every afternoon, about six o'clock, whatever the month or the season, and as a rule, little attention was paid to it. But to-day her sister Lilian responded, in a sympathetic voice,

"I wish we didn't have to live in a boarding-house!"

Whereupon Leicester, Lilian's twin brother, mimicking his sister's tones, dolefully repeated, "I wish we didn't have to live in a boarding-house!"

And then Fairy, the youngest Dorrance, and the last of the quartet, sighed forlornly, "I wish we didn't have to live in a boarding-house!"

There was another occupant of the room. A gentle white-haired old lady, whose sweet face and dainty fragile figure had all the effects of an ivory miniature, or a painting on porcelain.

"My dears," she said, "I'm sure I wish you didn't."

"Don't look like that, grannymother," cried Dorothy, springing to kiss the troubled face of the dear old lady. "I'd live here a million years, rather than have you look so worried about it. And anyway, it wouldn't be so bad, if it weren't for the dinners."

"I don't mind the dinners," said Leicester, "in fact I would be rather sorry not to have them. What I mind is the cramped space, and the shut-up-in-your-own-room feeling. I spoke a piece in school last week, and I spoke it awful well, too, because I just meant it. It began,'I want free life, and I want fresh air,' and that's exactly what I do want. I wish we lived in Texas, instead of on Manhattan Island. Texas has a great deal more room to the square yard, and I don't believe people are crowded down there."

"There can't be more room to a square yard in one place than another," said Lilian, who was practical.

"I mean back yards and front yards and side yards,—and I don't care whether they're square or not," went on Leicester, warming to his subject. "My air-castle is situated right in the middle of the state of Texas, and it's the only house in the state."

"Mine is in the middle of a desert island," said Lilian; "it's so much nicer to feel sure that you can get to the water, no matter in what direction you walk away from your house."

"A desert island would be nice," said Leicester; "it would be more exciting than Texas, I suppose, on account of the wild animals. But then in Texas, there are wild men and wild animals both."

"I like plenty of room, too," said Dorothy, "but I want it inside my house as well as out. Since we are choosing, I think I'll choose to live in the Madison Square Garden, and I'll have it moved to the middle of a western prairie."

"Well, children," said Mrs. Dorrance, "your ideas are certainly big enough, but you must leave the discussion of them now, and go to your small cramped boarding-house bedrooms, and make yourselves presentable to go down to your dinner in a boarding-house dining-room."

This suggestion was carried out in the various ways that were characteristic of the Dorrance children.

Dorothy, who was sixteen, rose from her chair and humming a waltz tune, danced slowly and gracefully across the room. The twins, Lilian and Leicester, fell off of the arms of the sofa, where they had been perched, scrambled up again, executed a sort of war-dance and then dashed madly out of the door and down the hall.

Fairy, the twelve year old, who lived up to her name in all respects, flew around the room, waving her arms, and singing in a high soprano, "Can I wear my pink sash? Can I wear my pink sash?"

"Yes, yes," said Mrs. Dorrance, "you may wear anything you like, if you'll only keep still a minute. You children are too boisterous for a boarding-house. You ought to be in the middle of a desert or somewhere. You bewilder me!"

But about fifteen minutes later it was four decorous young Dorrances who accompanied their grandmother to the dining-room. Not that they wanted to be sedate, or enjoyed being quiet, but they were well-bred children in spite of their rollicking temperaments. They knew perfectly well how to behave properly, and always did it when the occasion demanded.

And, too, the atmosphere of Mrs. Cooper's dining-room was an assistance rather than a bar to the repression of hilarity.

The Dorrances sat at a long table, two of the children on either side of their grandmother, and this arrangement was one of their chief grievances.

"If we could only have a table to ourselves," Leicester often said, "it wouldn't be so bad. But set up side by side, like the teeth in a comb, cheerful conversation is impossible."

"But, my boy," his grandmother would remonstrate, "you must learn to converse pleasantly with those who sit opposite you. You can talk with your sisters at other times."

So Leicester tried, but it is exceedingly difficult for a fourteen year old boy to adapt himself to the requirements of polite conversation.

On the evening of which we are speaking, his efforts, though well meant, were unusually unsuccessful.

Exactly opposite Leicester sat Mr. Bannister, a ponderous gentleman, both physically and mentally. He was a bachelor, and his only idea regarding children was that they should be treated jocosely. He also had his own ideas of jocose treatment.

"Well, my little man," he said, smiling broadly at Leicester, "did you go to school to-day?"

As he asked this question every night at dinner, not even excepting Saturdays and Sundays, Leicester felt justified in answering only, "Yes, sir."

"That's nice; and what did you learn?"

As this question invariably followed the other, Leicester was not wholly unprepared for it. But the discussion of air-castles in Texas, or on a prairie, had made the boy a little impatient of the narrow dining-room, and the narrow table, and even of Mr. Bannister, though he was by no means of narrow build.

"I learned my lessons," he replied shortly, though there was no rudeness in his tone.

"Tut, tut, my little man," said Mr. Bannister, playfully shaking a fat finger at him, "don't be rude."

"No, sir, I won't," said Leicester, with such an innocent air of accepting a general bit of good advice, that Mr. Bannister was quite discomfited.

Grandma Dorrance looked at Leicester reproachfully, and Mrs. Hill, who was a sharp-featured, sharp-spoken old lady, and who also sat on the other side of the table, said severely, to nobody in particular, "Children are not brought up now as they were in my day."

This had the effect of silencing Leicester, for the three older Dorrances had long ago decided that it was useless to try to talk to Mrs. Hill. Even if you tried your best to be nice and pleasant, she was sure to say something so irritating, that you just had to lose your temper.

But Fairy did not subscribe to this general decision. Indeed, Fairy's chief characteristic was her irrepressible loquacity. So much trouble had this made, that she had several times been forbidden to talk at the dinner-table at all. Then Grandma Dorrance would feel sorry for the dolefully mute little girl, and would lift the ban, restricting her, however, to not more than six speeches during any one meal.

Fairy kept strict account, and never exceeded the allotted number, but she made each speech as long as she possibly could, and rarely stopped until positively interrupted.

So she took it upon herself to respond to Mrs. Hill's remark, and at the same time demonstrate her loyalty to her grandmother.

"I'm sure, Mrs. Hill," Fairy began, "that nobody could bring up children better than my grannymother. She is the best children bring-upper in the whole world. I don't know how your grandmother brought you up,—or perhaps you had a mother,—some people think they're better than grandmothers. I don't know; I never had a mother, only a grandmother, but she's just the best ever, and if us children aren't good, it's our fault and not hers. She says we're boist'rous, and I 'spect we are. Mr. Bannister says we're rude, and I 'spect we are; but none of these objectionaries is grandma's fault!" Fairy had a way of using long words when she became excited, and as she knew very few real ones she often made them up to suit herself. And all her words, long or short came out in such a torrent of enthusiasm and emphasis, and with such a degree of rapidity that it was a difficult matter to stop her. So on she went. "So it's all right, Mrs. Hill, but when we don't behave just first-rate, or just as children did in your day, please keep a-remembering to blame us and not grandma. You see," and here Fairy's speech assumed a confidential tone, "we don't have room enough. We want free life and we want fresh air, and then I 'spect we'd be more decorious."

"That will do, Fairy," said Mrs. Dorrance, looking at her gravely.

"Yes'm," said Fairy, smiling pleasantly, "that'll do for one."

"And that makes two! now you've had two speeches, Fairy," said her brother, teasingly.

"I have not," said Fairy, "and an explanationary speech doesn't count!"

"Yes, it does," cried Lilian, "and that makes three!"

"It doesn't, does it, grandma?" pleaded Fairy, lifting her big blue eyes to her grandmother's face.

Mrs. Dorrance looked helpless and a little bewildered, but she only said, "Please be quiet, Fairy; I might like to talk a little, myself."

"Oh, that's all right, grandma dear," said Fairy, placidly; "I know how it is to feel conversationary myself."

The children's mother had died when Fairy was born, and her father had given her the name of Fairfax because there had always been a Fairfax Dorrance in his family for many generations. To be sure it had always before been a boy baby who was christened Fairfax, but the only boy in this family had been named Leicester; and so, one Fairfax Dorrance was a girl. From the time she was old enough to show any characteristics at all, she had been fairy-like in every possible way. Golden hair, big blue eyes and a cherub face made her a perfect picture of child beauty. Then she was so light and airy, so quick of motion and speech, and so immaculately dainty in her dress and person, that Fairy seemed to be the only fitting name for her. No matter how much she played rollicking games, her frock never became rumpled or soiled; and the big white bow which crowned her mass of golden curls always kept its shape and position even though its wearer turned somersaults. For Fairy was by no means a quiet or sedate child. None of the Dorrances were that. And the youngest was perhaps the most headstrong and difficult to control. But though impetuous in her deeds and mis-deeds, her good impulses were equally sudden, and she was always ready to apologize or make amends for her frequent naughtiness.

And so after dinner, she went to Mrs. Hill, and said with a most engaging smile, "I'm sorry if I 'fended you, and I hope I didn't. You see I didn't mean to speak so much, and right at the dinner table, too, but I just have to stand up for my grannymother. She's so old, and so ladylike that she can't stand up for herself. And I was 'fraid you mightn't understand, so I thought I'd 'pologize. Is it all right?"

Fairy looked up into Mrs. Hill's face with such angelic eyes and pleading smile, that even that dignified lady unbent a little.

"Yes, my dear," she said; "it's all right for you to stand up for your grandmother, as you express it. But you certainly do talk too much for such a little girl."

"Yes'm," said Fairy, contritely, "I know I do. It's my upsetting sin; but somehow I can't help it. My head seems to be full of words, and they just keep spilling out. Don't you ever talk too much, ma'am?"

"No; I don't think I do."

"You ought to be very thankful," said Fairy, with a sigh; "it is an awful affliction. Why once upon a time——"

"Come, Fairy," said Mrs. Dorrance; "say good-night to Mrs. Hill, and come up-stairs with me."

"Yes, grandma, I'm coming. Good-night, Mrs. Hill; I'm sorry I have to go just now 'cause I was just going to tell you an awful exciting story. But perhaps to-morrow——"

"Come, Fairy," said Mrs. Dorrance; "come at once!" And at last the gentle old lady succeeded in capturing her refractory granddaughter, and led the dancing sprite away to her own room.

2023-09-04 04:42:30 INFO - pageSourceWithSettingsEnd+++++++++++++++++++++++++ 2023-09-04 04:42:30 INFO - Taking screenshot 2023-09-04 04:42:31 INFO - Test finished - logging out 2023-09-04 04:42:33 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:42:35 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:42:36 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:42:37 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:42:39 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 04:42:39 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 04:42:39 INFO - Button 'Log out' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 04:43:00 INFO - Button 'Log in' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 04:43:00 INFO - Unlocking credential for current thread 2023-09-04 04:43:00 INFO - isLoggerNullAfterAnnotation-framework.utilities.Logger@1c7e34a7

2023-09-04 05:01:18 INFO - Scenario 'Font settings: Check of text theme' start 2023-09-04 05:01:18 INFO - Setting application driver using the server on 'https://hub-cloud.browserstack.com/wd/hub' 2023-09-04 05:01:45 INFO - Application on platform 'ANDROID' is ready... 2023-09-04 05:01:45 INFO - Session id - b17ee3a773ae2376b0c18a8ad46321c281c2e110 2023-09-04 05:01:45 INFO - Step 0 - Close tutorial screen 2023-09-04 05:01:45 INFO - Button 'btnCloseTutorial' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:01:47 INFO - Step 1 - Welcome screen is opened 2023-09-04 05:01:48 INFO - Step 2 - Close welcome screen 2023-09-04 05:01:48 INFO - Button 'btnFindLibrary' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:01:48 INFO - Step 3 - Add library screen is opened 2023-09-04 05:01:49 INFO - Step 4 - Add library "LYRASIS Reads" on Add library screen 2023-09-04 05:01:49 INFO - Button 'Search' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:01:50 INFO - Text Field 'Search' :: Clearing 2023-09-04 05:01:50 INFO - Text Field 'Search' :: Typing 'LYRASIS Reads' 2023-09-04 05:01:53 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:01:53 INFO - Step 5 - Account "LYRASIS Reads" is present on Accounts screen 2023-09-04 05:01:53 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:01:56 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:01:57 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:01:59 INFO - Step 6 - Enter credentials for 'LYRASIS Reads' account 2023-09-04 05:01:59 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:02:01 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:02:01 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:02:02 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:02:03 INFO - Locking credential with barcode 01230000000002 2023-09-04 05:02:03 INFO - There are books on the account: 2023-09-04 05:02:04 INFO - Books without revoke in link. BookName: Chocolate Cream Pie Murder Distributor: framework.utilities.returningBooksUtil.Distributor@1d414228 2023-09-04 05:02:04 INFO - Books without revoke in link. BookName: Unprotected Distributor: framework.utilities.returningBooksUtil.Distributor@7c8ef1d1 2023-09-04 05:02:04 INFO - bookName: The Innovators Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 05:02:04 INFO - bookName: Baby Carter Distributor: BiblioBoard 2023-09-04 05:02:04 INFO - bookName: The Martian Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 05:02:04 INFO - bookName: Legacy Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 05:02:04 INFO - bookName: The Black Kids Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 05:02:04 INFO - bookName: Phantom Lover Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 05:02:04 INFO - bookName: Snow Crash Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 05:02:04 INFO - bookName: The Ice Queen Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-04 05:02:04 INFO - Count of books on the account after opening account: 8 2023-09-04 05:02:04 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Clearing 2023-09-04 05:02:04 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Typing '01230000000002' 2023-09-04 05:02:06 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Clearing 2023-09-04 05:02:06 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Typing '********' 2023-09-04 05:02:08 INFO - Button 'Log in' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:02:13 INFO - Button 'Log ... action' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 05:02:13 INFO - Step 7 - Login is performed successfully 2023-09-04 05:02:34 INFO - Button 'Log ... action' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 05:02:34 INFO - Step 8 - Open Catalog 2023-09-04 05:02:34 INFO - Button 'tabCatalog' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:02:56 INFO - Step 9 - Open search modal 2023-09-04 05:03:16 INFO - Button 'Search' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:03:17 INFO - Step 10 - Search 'available' book of distributor 'Bibliotheca' and bookType 'EBOOK' from "LYRASIS Reads" and save as 'bookNameInfo' 2023-09-04 05:03:17 INFO - Count of attempts to get random book name without bad symbols-1 2023-09-04 05:03:17 INFO - randomBookName: The Secret Next Door 2023-09-04 05:03:18 INFO - Error details button is not present 2023-09-04 05:03:18 INFO - Text Field 'Search value input' :: Sending keys 'The Secret Next Door' 2023-09-04 05:03:21 INFO - Error details button is not present 2023-09-04 05:03:23 INFO - Step 11 - Click GET action button on EBOOK book with 'bookNameInfo' bookName on catalog books screen and save book as 'bookInfo' 2023-09-04 05:03:24 INFO - Label 'lblAuthor' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 05:03:24 INFO - Button 'actionButton' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:03:32 INFO - Step 12 - Open EBOOK book with READ action button and 'bookNameInfo' bookName on catalog books screen and save book as 'bookInfo' 2023-09-04 05:03:32 INFO - Label 'lblAuthor' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 05:03:32 INFO - Label 'lblBookName' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:03:33 INFO - Step 13 - Click READ action button on book details screen 2023-09-04 05:03:34 INFO - Button 'Read' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:03:35 INFO - Step 14 - Scroll page forward from 7 to 9 times 2023-09-04 05:03:35 INFO - Scrolling 7 times on reader epub screen 2023-09-04 05:03:51 INFO - Step 15 - Open font settings 2023-09-04 05:03:52 INFO - Button 'btnFontSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:03:52 INFO - Step 16 - Change contrast to BLACK_TEXT_ON_WHITE 2023-09-04 05:03:52 INFO - Button 'setThemeLight' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:03:53 INFO - Step 17 - The BLACK_TEXT_ON_WHITE background is correct 2023-09-04 05:03:53 INFO - context - NATIVE_APP 2023-09-04 05:03:53 INFO - context - WEBVIEW_org.thepalaceproject.palace 2023-09-04 05:03:55 INFO - pageSourceWithSettingsStart+++++++++++++++++++++++++ 2023-09-04 05:03:55 INFO -

Chapter Two

Bonnie Sloan sat behind the wheel of her Porsche and let her head fall back against the headrest. Anxiety clawed at her throat. She tried to breathe past it, swallow it down, but it felt tight, an insistence in her body that wanted to take flight into a full-blown panic.

She closed her eyes and tried to force her mind off the nasty particulars of the city council meeting she had just left and onto something more pleasant, calm—anything relaxing.

She tried to imagine herself on the beach in Maui eight years ago. She and her husband, Bennet, had rented that condo with the wide balcony that directly overlooked Kaanapali Beach, where her two sons had spent endless carefree hours playing in the sand and surf. George had been nine, Elijah only five—Gracie’s birth was still three years into the then distant future. Their lives had been so different then—simpler, really. Bonnie imagined herself on that plush teal-and-white-striped beach towel, the warm sand radiating up through her body and unwinding her every constricted muscle.

But Carl Wayland’s red and angry face swam up into her vision and interrupted her thoughts. “If you think for one second that I’ll allow that monstrosity to be erected in my backyard, you’ll be hearing from my lawyer!”

A massive wave of anxiety swept away her attempt at remembering happier times at the beach. Bonnie opened her eyes and stared out across the dark and deserted school parking lot she was hiding in. Tonight’s council meeting was the first public opportunity the community had to voice their thoughts about the Extreme Golf center breaking ground just west of The Enclave’s Highlands development, but Carl Wayland and his coalition of dissenters and complainers had been making their thoughts loud and clear all over The Enclave neighborhood’s Facebook page ever since the Extreme Golf land-use proposal had been filed with the city and made public three months ago.

Carl lived in the Highlands part of The Enclave—same as Bonnie. In fact, their multimillion-dollar homes were only one lot apart. Both their yards backed up to the third fairway of the Enclave golf course and enjoyed stunning and unobstructed views of the Rocky Mountains.

Views that would be forever altered as soon as Extreme Golf began erecting their two-hundred-foot steel beams and the netting system designed to catch golf balls flying from their five-story platform. And that was just during the day. At night, their floodlights would be seen for miles, completely obliterating the Highlands’s current serene atmosphere—and it wasn’t going to help the property values, either.

Bonnie understood Carl’s anger; after all, her house was going to be just as impacted as his. But as the elected city council official for Ward Eight, she couldn’t simply use her vote to the benefit of the wealthiest constituents with the largest houses and best views in the city.

Because on the opposite side from Carl were all the residents who really wanted Extreme Golf to move in. For the family-friendly entertainment they would get from launching golf balls from the fifth-floor decks while music blared and drinks were served, yes, but also for the tax revenue that would flow in for the city.

And, of course, Bonnie understood implicitly that many of her less wealthy constituents would derive some pleasure from sticking it to the Sloans and the Waylands of the world. She knew many residents saw Carl as an elitist who felt entitled to his multimillion-dollar unobstructed views, even though he did not personally own the land between his second-floor balcony and the Rocky Mountains. She and Bennet were both counting on Carl Wayland not being able to drum up much sympathy for his fight against Extreme Golf.

But Bonnie also understood that Carl Wayland had influential connections, deep pockets, and, as a retired CEO, nothing but time. Squashing the development of Extreme Golf in his backyard was now his full-time job.

And even though Bonnie would be staring, daily, at the same monstrosity while standing at her kitchen sink, sitting on her back patio, or gazing out her second-story master bedroom window, she could not let Carl Wayland stop this deal. No matter how much she personally would like to allow that to happen.

She had more at stake than a fabulous view and tens of thousands in resale value from her house.

Bennet was counting on her to shepherd the Extreme Golf deal through.

Bonnie checked the time on her phone: eight thirty. She needed to get home and see if the kids had eaten the dinner she left for them and if Bennet was home from work—the news about Carl and tonight’s meeting was going to send him over the edge.

She took a deep breath, started her car back up, and pulled out of the protective nighttime shadows of The Enclave’s K–8 charter school.

Whenever she was feeling overwhelmed and extremely stressed out, like right now, the darkest reaches of the school’s parking lot were where she always came to hide and think. She had discovered it entirely by accident, years ago, when her middle child, Elijah, was in second grade. Back then, she’d been president of the PTA. Often the first to arrive and the last to leave the school during every function.

It had been the October parent-teacher conferences, and she and the rest of the PTA were running the bookfair in the school’s library. Sometime after eight, she had walked out to the parking lot with the last few teachers in the building. By the time she loaded up her trunk, got behind the wheel of her car, and discovered that her battery was dead, everyone else had already pulled out of sight.

The very first emotion that hit her was fear. She was a woman alone, in the dark, in a car that wouldn’t start. Everything about her life up to this moment had trained her to believe she was on the verge of being raped, abducted, or, at the very least, robbed. Never mind that she was in the neighborhood she’d lived in, at the time, for fifteen years. Sitting in her car, doors locked, behind tinted windows so dark no one could see her, especially at night.

Bonnie had sat back in her seat and picked up her phone, ready to call Bennet to come rescue her, when another feeling hit her. An emotion so foreign to her current life, she almost couldn’t name it.

Calm.

Maybe it wasn’t exactly calm, but it was near enough to a sense of well-being, something she hadn’t experienced in over a decade, that it grabbed her attention.

She was a woman, alone in the dark.

And no one could see her.

Bonnie had stopped dialing her husband and put her phone down.

She sat back in her seat, feeling the muscles that normally roped across her shoulder blades release a fraction of an inch, and noticed how the glow of light from the streetlamps in front of the school didn’t reach to the farthest corners of the parking lot. She felt invisible to the outside world, and it felt good. Regularly, eyes followed her everywhere she went.

At five foot eight, with a slender build, C-cup breasts, and a ballet dancer’s ass, Bonnie Sloan knew she was a beautiful woman. She held herself erect, wore the right clothes, drove a luxury car, and occupied the home that, situated off the third fairway on a slight rise, was visible to everyone entering The Enclave from the main entrance. Her home was the crown jewel of the Enclave development.

Eyes, they were on her, always. Even in her own home, between Bennet and her three kids, rarely was there ever a moment or a space to herself.

But not here. In this one dark parking space where no one would ever look for her. Here she could, and had, eaten an entire Big Mac, large fries, and a regular Coke. She slouched, belched, and often even passed gas without giving it any thought at all. No one was watching, ever, as long as she was alone, here in the dark.

So when tonight’s city council meeting was essentially commandeered by Carl Wayland and several of her other neighbors, she knew she’d need to make a stop before heading home and sharing the news with Bennet.

The Extreme Golf development was not going to go off without a hitch. And if she was going to pull off her run for the Senate, she and Bennet were going to have to be smart, get out in front of the growing public conflict on the right side, and play all their cards well.

Because if Carl Wayland dug around deep enough to discover the truth that he already suspected, it would ruin her and her family.

2023-09-04 05:03:55 INFO - pageSourceWithSettingsEnd+++++++++++++++++++++++++ 2023-09-04 05:03:55 INFO - Taking screenshot 2023-09-04 05:03:57 INFO - Test finished - logging out 2023-09-04 05:03:58 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:04:00 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:04:02 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:04:02 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:04:05 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 05:04:05 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 05:04:05 INFO - Button 'Log out' :: Clicking 2023-09-04 05:04:26 INFO - Button 'Log in' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-04 05:04:26 INFO - Unlocking credential for current thread 2023-09-04 05:04:26 INFO - isLoggerNullAfterAnnotation-framework.utilities.Logger@1c7e34a7